(Sheldon:)What would be your plan
for addressing it?
(Amy:)I'm going to recondition your brain...
(Amy:)...so that the need for completion
isn't be so overwhelming.
- By playing tic-tac-toe?
- Yep, your turn.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Amy. And you wonder why
people think neuroscience...
(Sheldon:)...is nothing but a goofy game
for diaper babies.
(Sheldon:)Tic-tac-toe can only end
in win, lose or draw.
(Sheldon:)None of which will deny me closure,
especially since I'm about to win.
(Sheldon:)But we didn't finish.
(Amy:)Exactly. How does that make you feel?
(Sheldon:)The same way
any normal person would.
Feel like I wanna peel off my own face,
tear it in two and then again and again...
(Sheldon:)...until I have a handful of
Sheldon-face confetti.